A Finding Aid to the Architectural League of New York Records, 1880s-1974, bulk 1927-1968, in the Archives of American Art AAA.archleag
Archives of American Art
- Committee Records, 1887-1974; Series 2; 44.7 Linear feet Boxes 10-54, 110, 114, OV 116
  - House Committee, 1889-1969; 2.3
    - Plans for League Headquarters at 115 East 40th Street, 1961; (Oversized material from Box 22, Folder 5) (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Repairs and Additions, 1921, 1933; (Oversized materials from Box 22, Folder 36) (Box OV 116)
  - Finance Committee, 1895-1972; 2.4
    This subseries includes balance sheets, budgets, financial statements, a ledger, two journals, meeting minutes, office vouchers, payroll records, tax records, Treasurer's files, and other records related to overseeing the dispersal of funds and the finances of the League. Also found is the bulk of the records in the collection related to the 21-year collateral note bought by the League in the late 1920s. Similar materials can be found in Business Records series.
    - Accounts Payable, 1933-1965 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Accounts Receivable, 1951-1953 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Accounts Receivable, 1961-1965 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Accounts Receivable, Members, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Accounts Receivable, Proofs, 1946-1947 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Accounts Receivable and Comparative Balance Sheets, 1965-1966 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Advisory Finance Committee, 1933, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Agendas, 1934-1950; (4 folders) (Box 26, Folder 14-17)
    - Annual Billing, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Audit Reports, 1921-1964; (7 folders) (Box 26, Folder 19-25)
    - Audit Reports, 1921-1964; (11 folders) (Box 27, Folder 1-11)
    - Auditing, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Auditor, 1965-1967 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Auditor, Robert L. Henry, 1937-1942 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Auditor, Pellaton, Bilton and Tuck, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - (Back) Interest Due on Notes, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Balance Sheets, 1942-1954 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Balance Sheets [C. Dale Badgeley], 1964-1966 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Bills, Bachman Offset Printing, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Blaikie-Hines Survey Report (Apr. 1950) (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Brown Brothers Harriman and Co., 1939 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Budget Reports, 1948-1966; (2 folders) (Box 27, Folder 22-23)
    - Budget Studies, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Budgets, 1944-1951; (3 folders) (Box 27, Folder 25-27)
    - Cash Deposited, 1933-1935 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Chairman, Henry C. Eipel, 1955, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Check Stub Book, 1963-1964; (2 folders) (Box 27, Folder 30-31)
    - Collateral Note (Box 27)
      - Bond Circulars, 1936-1942 (Box 27, Folder 32)
      - Bonds Miscellaneous, 1927-1948 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Collateral Note (Box 28)
      - Bonds Miscellaneous, 1927-1948; (2 folders) (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
      - Central Hanover Bank and Trust, 1928-1931 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1927-1953; (26 folders) (Box 28, Folder 4-29)
      - Correspondence, H-Y, 1927-1950; (14 folders) (Box 28, Folder 30-43)
    - Collateral Note (Box 29)
      - Correspondence, H-Y, 1927-1950; (7 folders) (Box 29, Folder 1-7)
      - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1927-1960; (2 folders) (Box 29, Folder 8-9)
      - Correspondence, Outgoing, 1942, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Gold Notes Due Nov. 1, 1948, circa 1948 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Legal Documents and Miscellaneous, 1909, 1927-1947; (3 folders) (Box 29, Folder 12-14)
      - Releases or Transfers of Bonds, Receipts, 1934-1940 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - Subscriptions (1927), 1927-1932; (3 folders) (Box 29, Folder 16-18)
      - Transferred Bonds, 1929, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - Treasurer 1927-1928, Bonds Issued - List of Subscribers (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - Treasurer 1933-1934, Affidavit of Mailing (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - Treasurer 1933-1934, Bond Holders - List of League, circa 1933-1934 (Box 29, Folder 22)
      - Treasurer 1933-1934, Return of Bonds for Dues (Box 29, Folder 23)
      - Treasurer 1933-1934, Waivers - Resolution Approving (Box 29, Folder 24)
      - Treasurer 1933-1934, Waivers and Forms (Box 29, Folder 25)
      - Treasurer 1934-1935, 1934, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Collecting Membership Dues, 1939-1942 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Committee Expense Reports, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Comparative Balance Sheets, 1949-1966; (10 folders) (Box 29, Folder 29-38)
    - Comparative Balance Sheets, 1949-1966; (4 folders) (Box 30, Folder 1-4)
    - Contracts Paid, 1951-1952 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Contributions to League, 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1939-1940, 1950; (2 folders) (Box 30, Folder 7-8)
    - Correspondence, S, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Current Charges, 1951 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Daily Invoice Sheets (1953, March-April) (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Estimated Expenses, 1933-1949 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Estimated Receipts and Disbursements (Mar. 14 - Apr. 15, 1950) (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Expenditures, Miscellaneous, 1943, 1962-1965 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Federal Legislation, Tariff Laws for Works of Art, 1959, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Funds, 1958-1965 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Funds (Box 30)
      - Designated Funds, 1955-1965 (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Scudder, Stevens and Clark Balanced Fund, 1950-1969 (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - Statements of Funds, 1955-1964 (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - Various, 1963-1968 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - General Ledger (Apr. 1, 1945 - Mar. 31, 1948), 1945-1948 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - House Committee, Special Loan, 1928-1934 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Journals (1948-1954; 1954-1962), 1948-1962; (2 folders) (Box 30, Folder 23-24)
    - Memo re: Special Funds, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Minutes of Finance Committee Meetings, 1935-1964; (6 folders) (Box 30, Folder 26-31)
    - Minutes of Finance Committee Meetings, 1935-1964; (12 folders) (Box 31, Folder 1-12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1927-1967, undated; (4 folders) (Box 31, Folder 13-16)
    - Notes Payable (To 1941), 1933-1941 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Notes Payable, Architects Offices, Inc., 1939-1951 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Notes Payable, Miscellaneous, 1941-1947 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Notices of Finance Committee Meetings, 1948-1960; (2 folders) (Box 31, Folder 20-21)
    - Office Vouchers, 1935-1972; (31 folders) (Box 31, Folder 22-52)
    - Office Vouchers, 1935-1972; (16 folders) (Box 32, Folder 1-16)
    - Operational Information, 1927-1939 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Petty Cash Ledger, 1957-1961 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Proposed Budgets, 1934-1964; (3 folders) (Box 33, Folder 1-3)
    - Rendering Book, Minor L. Bishop Accounts, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Report on Accounts to Executive Committee, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Report for Distribution (Executive Committee), 1949-1950 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Republic of Chile, Schroder Trust Co. (Bonds), 1946-1949 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Secretary 1933-1934, Clippings, circa 1933-1934 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Secretary 1938-1939, Bills (City and State Legislation) (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Securities, 1931, 1946-1947 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Securities, Scudder, Stevens and Clark, 1952-1966; (4 folders) (Box 33, Folder 11-14)
    - Securities Owned by the League, 1931-1942 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Shearson Capital Fund, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Statements of Operations, 1931-1948; (8 folders) (Box 33, Folder 17-24)
    - Stock Information, 1953-1964 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Tax (Box 33)
      - Excise Tax Returns, 1936-1946 (Box 33, Folder 26)
      - Floor Stocks Tax Return, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 27)
      - Forms [Blank], 1952 (Box 33, Folder 28)
      - Internal Revenue, 1954-1959 (Box 33, Folder 29)
      - Land Taxes and Paid Bills, 1955-1966 (Box 33, Folder 30)
      - New York City Withholding Tax, 1966-1969 (Box 33, Folder 31)
      - New York State Sales Tax, 1959-1965 (Box 33, Folder 32)
      - New York State Withholding Tax for Quarterly Reports, 1959-1969 (Box 33, Folder 33)
      - Occupancy Tax Reports, 1950, 1955-1964; (2 folders) (Box 33, Folder 34-35)
      - Signs, 1936-1937 (Box 33, Folder 36)
      - Social Security, 1937-1959; (2 folders) (Box 33, Folder 37-38)
      - Social Security Exemption, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 39)
      - Special Tax Return (re: Federal Retail Liquor), 1937 (Box 33, Folder 40)
      - Tax-Exempt Organization, 1951-1966 (Box 33, Folder 41)
      - Tax Exemption (Office of Internal Revenue), 1934-1938 (Box 33, Folder 42)
      - Treasury Department, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Tax, Water Tax, 1928-1965; (4 folders) (Box 34, Folder 1-4)
    - Tax Guides, 1960-1966 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Treasurer [1929-1930], Special Loan (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Treasurer 1933-1934, Audit Reports, (2 folders) (Box 34, Folder 7-8)
    - Treasurer 1934-1935, 50th Exhibition of the League Entrance Fee Paid, 1933-1936 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Treasurer 1934-1935, 50th Exhibition of the League Entrance Fee Refunds, 1933-1936 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Treasurer 1935-1936, Bills Correspondence, 1933-1936 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Treasurer 1939-1940, Audit Reports (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Treasurer 1943, Annual Report, 1943-1944 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Treasurer's Reports, 1895-1908, 1935; (2 folders) (Box 34, Folder 14-15)
    - U.S. Treasury Department, 1946-1965 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Work Complete, 1955-1956; (5 folders) (Box 34, Folder 17-21)
    - Work Complete, 1955-1956; (12 folders) (Box 35, Folder 1-12)
  - Membership Committee, 1897-1972; 2.5
    The Membership Committee records document League membership from the late 1890s to 1972 through membership applications, resignation and transfer records, dues payments, mailing lists, address changes for members, and correspondence. Also found are meeting minutes, committee chairman's files, Secretary's files, and other administrative records. Additional membership-related correspondence is found in the Correspondence Series.
    - 25-Year Members (as of June 1, 1947) (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Active Members, circa 1950s (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Address Changes, 1943-1968; (8 folders) (Box 35, Folder 15-22)
    - Address Changes, 1943-1968; (4 folders) (Box 36, Folder 1-4)
    - Address Changes (Box 36)
      - A-Z, 1950-1951; (4 folders) (Box 36, Folder 5-8)
      - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Etc. to Bachman Offset Printing, 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Forms, circa 1950 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Mail Returned, 1941-1942, 1955-1956; (2 folders) (Box 36, Folder 12-13)
      - Questionnaire, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Agendas and Notices of Membership Committee Meetings, 1950-1954 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Agendas and Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Agendas of Committees, 1958-1961 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Allowance by Cards Signed, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Annual Membership Report, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Applicants for Employment, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Assessment Meeting Minutes, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Assessments, 1951-1952 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Bachman Offset Printing Corrections, 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Bills Requested from Miss Schwarz for New Associate Members, 1950-1951 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Biographical Information About Members, 1957, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Budgets, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Chairman (Box 36)
      - Adams, Lewis G., Membership Committee Members, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - Butt, Alfred, Jr., 1941-1949, 1961; (3 folders) (Box 36, Folder 28-30)
      - Geiffert, Alfred (Special), 1936-1937 (Box 36, Folder 31)
      - Hutchins, Robert S., 1948-1949 (Box 36, Folder 32)
      - Radoslovich, Michael, 1961, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 33)
      - Walbridge, Cole B., 1951-1961; (3 folders) (Box 36, Folder 34-36)
    - Chairman (Box 37)
      - Walbridge, Cole B., 1951-1961; (2 folders) (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
      - Williams, Wheeler, circa 1939-1940 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Woodbridge, Frederick, 1937-1938 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Chairmen, 1956-1957 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Changes in Category of Membership Pre Apr. 1969, Bachman Offset Printing, 1968-1969 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Changes in Category of Membership Since Apr. 1969 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Changes in Membership Status According to New Constitution, 1947-1948 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Christmas Bonus, 1968-1970; (2 folders) (Box 37, Folder 9-10)
    - Committee Chairmen, Minutes of Special Committee, 1958 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1941-1970; (13 folders) (Box 37, Folder 12-24)
    - Correspondence (Box 37)
      - A-Z, 1950-1951 (Box 37, Folder 25)
      - Active, 1954-1961 (Box 37, Folder 26)
      - Applications (New), 1937-1938 (Box 37, Folder 27)
      - Art Gallery Magazine and Other Magazines, circa 1968-1969 (Box 37, Folder 28)
      - Delinquent Dues, 1936-1939 (Box 37, Folder 29)
      - Delinquent Dues, 1951-1953 (Box 37, Folder 30)
      - Delinquent Dues Letter (Sent Oct. 30, 1958) (Box 37, Folder 31)
      - Delinquent Letter re: Dues (Jan. 28, 1958), 1957-1960 (Box 37, Folder 32)
      - Follow Up, 1940 (Box 37, Folder 33)
      - Follow-Up and File, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 34)
      - Olindo Grossi, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 35)
      - Edgar W. Hatfield, Attorney, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 36)
      - Robert Hutchins, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 37)
      - Mary Huzar, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 38)
      - Letter to Helen Treadwell re: Dues, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 39)
      - Letter to Members re: Bar Renovation, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 40)
      - Letters Inviting Members to Work on Committees, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 41)
      - Letters re: Delinquent Dues (Active and Non-Resident), 1952-1958 (Box 37, Folder 42)
      - Letters re: Lapsed Membership (A.W. Butt), 1947-1949 (Box 37, Folder 43)
      - Letters to About-to-be-Posted Members (Oct. 19, 1951) (Box 37, Folder 44)
      - Letters to Delinquent Members, 1951-1966; (3 folders) (Box 37, Folder 45-47)
      - Letters to Firms re: Membership, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence (Box 38)
      - Letters to Members Delinquent in Dues, 1953-1956 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Letters to Members re: Dues, 1951-1954; (2 folders) (Box 38, Folder 2-3)
      - Letters to Students re: Memberships, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - William Luttrell, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - New Committee Members, 1956-1960 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Outgoing to Members, 1951-1954; (2 folders) (Box 38, Folder 7-8)
      - President's Letters to Members, 1966-1967 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - R, 1936-1941 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Re: Designation of Profession of Members, 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Daniel Schwartzman, 1961-1963 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Robert Fitch Smith, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Special Letter to Members Considering Resignation, 1960-1964 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Student Dues, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Vice Presidents, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Vice Presidents, Letters re: Delinquent Members, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Delinquent Dues, 1950; (7 folders) (Box 38, Folder 18-24)
    - Delinquent Dues Notice, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Delinquent Dues Payers (Since Apr. 1969), 1960s (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Delinquent List (as of January 27, 1954), 1954-1958 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Dues, 1933-1967; (10 folders) (Box 38, Folder 28-37)
    - Dues, Delinquent Letters, 1954, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Dues, Delinquent Letters to Non-Residents, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Dues Collection, 1936-1940 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Dues Collection, Deceased Members, 1949 (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Dues and Miscellaneous, 1954-1966; (2 folders) (Box 38, Folder 42-43)
    - Dues Payment, 1938, 1949-1950, 1954; (4 folders) (Box 38, Folder 44-47)
    - Dues Payment, Acknowledgements, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 48)
    - Dues Suspension, 1951-1954 (Box 38, Folder 49)
    - Executive Committee Meeting Regarding League Move, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 50)
    - Form Letters, 1934-1937, 1947-1950; (2 folders) (Box 38, Folder 51-52)
    - Form Letters for Delinquent Accounts, 1948-1950 (Box 38, Folder 53)
    - Form Letters for Membership, 1938-1943 (Box 38, Folder 54)
    - Form Letters to Delinquent Members, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - General Membership Meeting (June 22, 1964) (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Guest Cards, 1948-1949 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Guest Cards Issued, 1947-1948 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Guest Cards Requested and Issued, 1939-1942 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Inaugural Reception, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Inaugural Reception (May 14, 1970) (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Insurance Brochures, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Invitations to Join League, 1938-1955; (4 folders) (Box 39, Folder 9-12)
    - Invitations to Join League (Draft), 1954 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Invitations to Join League (A. Fitzhugh), 1939 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Invitations to Membership, 1955-1961 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Invitations to Membership Committee, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Invited, 1949-1951 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Invited, Mr. Geiffert, 1936-1937 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Invited to Join League, Cannot Accept, 1937-1938 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Invited to Join League, Pending, 1937-1938 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Invited to Join League, Replies, 1936-1937 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Invited to Join League by Executive Committee as Associate or Non-Resident, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Invited to Join League (Since Feb. 1, 1939 to Sept. 1940), 1938-1940 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Lay Membership, circa 1948 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Lay Membership Elected, 1936-1964 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - League Wives, 1938-1941 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Letters From Membership Chair to League, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Letters of Request and Letters of Invitation, 1961 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Letters to Members (Lapsed), 1971 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Letters to Patrons, 1964-1966 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Letters to Potential Members, 1961-1964 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Lists of Delinquents, 1952-1954; (2 folders) (Box 39, Folder 32-33)
    - Lists of Members, 1941-1969, undated; (5 folders) (Box 39, Folder 34-38)
    - Lists of Members Paid and Unpaid, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Lists of Members Requesting Resignations, 1927, 1934 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - Lists of New Members, 1949-1960; (3 folders) (Box 39, Folder 41-43)
    - Lists of New Members and Sponsors, 1952-1960 (Box 39, Folder 44)
    - Lists of Sculptor Members, 1943, 1949; (2 folders) (Box 39, Folder 45-46)
    - Lists of Sculptor, Painter and New Members, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 47)
    - Magazine and Book Discounts, 1968-1969 (Box 39, Folder 48)
    - Mailing Lists, Prospective Members, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 49)
    - Mailings to Membership By Other Organizations, 1969-1970 (Box 39, Folder 50)
    - Member Cards, circa 1941 (Box 39, Folder 51)
    - Member Cards, Diagrams Submitted by Gustave Jensen, circa 1950; (Oversized materials housed in Box 110, Folder 2) (Box 39, Folder 52)
    - Member Show, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 53)
    - Member Statistics, 1945-1946 (Box 39, Folder 54)
    - Members [circa 1968], A-Z, 1935-1968; (2 folders) (Box 39, Folder 55-56)
    - Members [circa 1968], A-Z, 1935-1968; (5 folders) (Box 40, Folder 1-5)
    - Members (Box 40)
      - Active, 1944-1966; (3 folders) (Box 40, Folder 6-8)
      - Associates, 1949, 1953; (2 folders) (Box 40, Folder 9-10)
      - Associates Dropped, 1953 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Deceased, 1935-1970; (12 folders) (Box 40, Folder 12-23)
      - Delinquent, 1946-1954; (5 folders) (Box 40, Folder 24-28)
      - Delinquent - Active, 1950, 1957; (2 folders) (Box 40, Folder 29-30)
      - Delinquent - Associate, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 31)
      - Delinquent - For Bill Collectors, 1953 (Box 40, Folder 32)
      - Delinquent - Non-Resident, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 33)
      - Delinquent - Pending, 1948-1950 (Box 40, Folder 34)
      - Delinquent - Sundries, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 35)
      - Dropped, 1936-1938, circa 1947-1949; (5 folders) (Box 40, Folder 36-40)
      - Dropped - Active, 1938-1964; (2 folders) (Box 40, Folder 41-42)
      - Dropped - Associate, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 43)
    - Members (Box 41)
      - Dropped - Junior, circa 1953-1954 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Dropped - Lay, circa 1953-1954 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Dropped - Mail Returned, 1938-1940 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Dropped - Non-Resident, 1950-1954; (2 folders) (Box 41, Folder 4-5)
      - Dropped for Delinquent Dues - Associate, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Dropped for Delinquent Dues - Lay, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Dropped for Delinquent Dues - Non-Resident, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Dropped for Non-Payment of Dues (Apr. 1969), 1950s-1969 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Dropped or Resignations Accepted Subject to Payment of Dues-Who Have Made Payment, 1948 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Easel Painters, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Members, Emeritus, 1920s-1972; (8 folders) (Box 41, Folder 12-19)
      - Foreign, Non-Resident, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Honorary, 1937-1962; (2 folders) (Box 41, Folder 21-22)
      - Junior, 1938, 1951-1952; (2 folders) (Box 41, Folder 23-24)
      - Lay, 1939-1966; (3 folders) (Box 41, Folder 25-27)
      - New, 1959-1961, 1971-1972; (2 folders) (Box 41, Folder 28-29)
      - New - #1, 1936-1937 (Box 41, Folder 30)
      - New - Executive Committee, 1936-1938 (Box 41, Folder 31)
      - New (Nov. 1, 1948 - July 20, 1949) (Box 41, Folder 32)
      - New (Since Jan. 1944), 1945 (Box 41, Folder 33)
      - Non-Resident, 1952-1966; (3 folders) (Box 41, Folder 34-36)
      - Non-Resident Applications, 1950-1952 (Box 41, Folder 37)
      - Non-Resident Delinquents, 1952-1956, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 38)
      - Non-Residents Elected After Apr. 1, 1948, 1943-1949 (Box 41, Folder 39)
      - Reinstated, 1936-1950; (3 folders) (Box 41, Folder 40-42)
      - Reinstated - Re-elected, 1949-1950 (Box 41, Folder 43)
      - Reinstated (After April 1, 1948), 1947-1948 (Box 41, Folder 44)
      - Reinstated (To Mar. 30, 1948) (Box 41, Folder 45)
      - Reinstatements, 1945-1966; (2 folders) (Box 41, Folder 46-47)
      - Reinstatements - Non-Resident, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 48)
      - Students, 1952-1964; (2 folders) (Box 41, Folder 49-50)
      - Suspended, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 51)
      - Women, 1941-1948; (4 folders) (Box 41, Folder 52-55)
    - Members Accounts Receivable, 1939, 1951-1964; (9 folders) (Box 41, Folder 56-64)
    - Members Owing Amounts, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 65)
    - Members Recently Invited to Return (May 17, 1949), 1947-1949 (Box 41, Folder 66)
    - Membership 1939-1940, Circulars, circa 1939-1940 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Membership Applications, 1897-1969; (13 folders) (Box 42, Folder 2-14)
    - Membership Applications (Box 42)
      - A-Z, 1897-1965; (11 folders) (Box 42, Folder 15-25)
      - A-Z, 1897-1965; (22 folders) (Box 43, Folder 1-22)
      - Active, 1950-1951 (Box 43, Folder 23)
      - Blank, 1951, circa 1960s-1972, undated; (3 folders) (Box 43, Folder 24-26)
      - [Collated], A-Z, 1897-1922; (3 folders) (Box 43, Folder 27-29)
      - [Collated], A-Z, 1897-1922; (3 folders) (Box 44, Folder 1-3)
      - New Since Dec. 8, 1938 (Fitzhugh), 1938-1939 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Rejected, 1947-1948, 1950; (2 folders) (Box 44, Folder 5-6)
      - Rejected or Recalled, 1949 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Samples and Drafts, circa 1959 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Uncompleted, 1950-1951 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Withdrawn, 1947 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Membership Applications and Resignations, 1936-1969; (6 folders) (Box 44, Folder 11-16)
    - Membership Applications and Resignations, E-W, 1934-1966; (12 folders) (Box 44, Folder 17-28)
    - Membership Book, 1951-1952 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Membership Book [edited version], circa 1960 (Box 44, Folder 30)